We call it a conference.
Yeah.
You gotta know what you're doing.
I have to have to.
I recall it called or the regorscut committee
Miles City Council for Monday to celebrate
2023.
But again put or unscathed personal
bances.
Kindlist.
I think we should go.
Second.
Third.
Instead.
Second.
I'm going to make a motion to approve it, take it.
Is that right?
It's still cold.
Stay.
Hi.
Williams?
Are you saying no?
I am.
I guess you're probably going to need to stay for this one too, don't you?
Are you going to do this one?
Six for new contracts.
C22.
Richard Wilson for Mowing and Bailing of the Public Property.
I'd recommend about that.
Because like we just did this last year.
We did it.
So it was awarded in 2022.
It has four when your lease extensions.
So we're just asking for this.
Second.
Hi.
Is that?
Williams.
I'm seven.
Hi.
There appears to be some discrepancies in the numbers for one.
Norther.
To ensure the city is provided to best possible bid.
I suggest we take no action on.
I don't know.
I'm seven.
Give them up.
Can I do that.
Get the kids.
So I want to do that.
Thank you.
Does it make a motion?
Eight.
Marron, Maria.
Marron.
to a point Jeff Howe to the airport authority replacing Jess Robinson, turn to expire
11 7 24.
10.
Earlier this year, we being involved in the Attorney General's
with the ORE settlement process.
This is another one.
We haven't heard from any kind of specializing this areas.
And don't get out of it.
This is a settlement.
Different company than the companies that the Attorney General
We've been settled with, since we haven't heard anything.
We don't see a reason for us to hop out.
But the decision that we knocked out, then we decided we wanted to.
How many other people are in it?
Do you know?
I do.
We talked about this month or two ago.
The same similar deal.
Different companies.
And that one was through the Attorney General's office.
This is a different class action lawsuit.
But we're already in it.
We don't know if any reason my reason popped out.
The last one had to do with water contamination.
You know, that's another one.
That's a third one.
Yeah.
That's all clear as much.
It's always been your recommendation as we stay in.
One is we have no reason to get out.
But we would have the option later to get out if we'd so chunks.
But I'm propped it out.
It is unbelievable.
It is.
Monday.
That's the thing I'm saying.
January 5th.
But we have another meeting.
We will have one of the Senator.
We have another meeting.
So we have till the second.
If anything else comes up, we could opt out by then.
We could opt out.
Okay.
But we just want to be on my way.
That's where there's yet another one.
So, I guess we want to request the not date from you or our next meeting.
I think that's fair.
You can't see anything really.
Sometimes with people fromencer CMT.
Or, like, this is pretty government ceremony.
I think.
But it is.
than you complain.
Dis googleет.
Because i've heard about quality cosmetic.
People from onatio the internet.
So unless somebody contacts us.
So.
Unless somebody contacts us.
And that's kind of why I think we're out here.
Whether they don't get to say it.
But then next meeting.
Just in case.
Something like the last thing came up.
We have another information.
No, no.
Any other questions for Ben?
You know?
I love it.
I'm going to do a business with any of which that represents the supposed to this agenda.
12 staff reports, 13 mayor and council community announcements.
To him, Ron, you're way too.
I don't know if I happened to do anything this time.
I hadn't had anything going on.
Tell him I could play.
Oh yeah, I was Jesus in our church Christmas play.
I went well, had a good time, good turnout, parking lot was packed, the seats were packed.
So it was good.
That's all I got.
Well, you know, we're wrapping up a year that really went well, of course.
I had a lot of good things happen to my office here and thank the train to roll into the
road direction and appreciate staff and all your efforts.
We couldn't do it without you.
You guys are driving this thing, we're just along for the ride, we appreciate all your efforts.
So keep it up, we'll keep doing what we do and just keep the teamwork going and might my own better
place this next year too.
So I appreciate everybody, the city, take your crews, I appreciate all of them, just
proud of that.
And Mary, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
All of that?
I think we've had not only a fantastic year, but we're ending it here in the calendar year with a great holiday season.
We've got a big, beautiful tree on Main Street with a great turnout.
I've heard that's the tallest tree on the street.
We had a great parade with an open-up that we had a holiday market that was fantastic
while attended with a rain there on Main Street.
The Main Street is packed with a sip and shop.
That was fantastic turnout for them.
The new light and LED balls hanging on Main Street look beautiful.
Tyler's not here to thank for that, but all the hoax, the Osborne drug and Bill Osborne and Cody
for all their hard work on that.
It's just really been a neat holiday season.
We had great events at the Coleman that were all well attended, Christmas Carol, even to show
on Sunday.
We had a rapport to be, but it shouldn't have to watch it.
It's a wonderful opportunity.
And the numbers are strong at the Coleman.
So, and we're ending the year in a positive note with our sales tax.
But it's a good calendar year.
Tell us a scooter story.
So, during our ribbon cutting the other day, the owner of our local scooter store.
We were talking about it and then bragging about, you know, his success he had on opening day,
which, you know, blew away as a scooter store.
I think he held story up there.
But he didn't do so this year.
And this has been a real strong opening weekend and week.
And they were just doing great.
But he said, the coolest thing was they had a national meeting of sorts where...
The meaning of the areas represented in all the orders were there, and the President of the
Scooters Corporation, sealed him out and said, what in the hell is going on in my
O'clock?
He said, there is a sudden special happen there, and he just said, he was just thought that
was so cool that the President, so he doesn't know from out, found him in the point of
him out, so what's going on?
And he said, yep, there's sudden special going on there.
That was really cool.
And I'll tell you, I know something about time, but the Scooters, the owner of Scooters said
that he had 180 applicants, and the guy at seven brews said he had over 300, and then
Jane and Parnas were telling us they're not having any trouble getting employees right
now either, so tell them that people are going back to work, so he needs to be in charge
of the team.